Council on Foreign Relations Records: Studies Department Series, 1918-2004: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Subseries 3C: Staffing, 1925-2004; 32.32 linear feet 78 boxes
  - Diebold, William, 1925-2000; 50 boxes (1 partial)
    - Correspondence, 1935-2000; 21 boxes
      - Chronological, 1958-1983; 18 boxes (1 partial)
        - 1966, portions of 2 boxes
          - F, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 351, Folder 9)
          - G, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 351, Folder 10)
          - H, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 351, Folder 11)
          - I-J, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 351, Folder 12)
          - K, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 351, Folder 13)
          - L, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 351, Folder 14)
          - Ma-Me, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 351, Folder 15)
          - Mi-Mu, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 351, Folder 16)
          - Mc, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 351, Folder 17)
          - N, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 351, Folder 18)
          - O, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 1)
          - P-Q, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 2)
          - R, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 3)
          - Sa-Sn, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 4)
          - So-Sz, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 5)
          - T, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 6)
          - U-V, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 7)
          - W, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 8)
          - X-Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 9)
        - 1967, portions of 2 boxes
          - A, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 10)
          - B, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 11)
          - C, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 12)
          - D, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 13)
          - E, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 14)
          - F, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 15)
          - G, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 16)
          - H, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 17)
          - I-J, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 18)
          - K, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 19)
          - L, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 20)
          - Ma-Me, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 21)
          - Mi-Mu, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 22)
          - Mc, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 23)
          - N, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 24)
          - O, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 25)
          - P-Q, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 26)
          - R, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 27)
          - Sa-Sn, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 1)
          - So-Sz, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 2)
          - T, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 3)
          - U-V, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 4)
          - W, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 5)
          - X-Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 6)
        - 1968, 25 folders
          - A, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 7)
          - B, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 8)
          - C, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 9)
          - D, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 10)
          - E, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 11)
          - F, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 12)
          - G, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 13)
          - H, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 14)
          - I, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 15)
          - J, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 16)
          - K, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 17)
          - L, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 18)
          - Ma-Me, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 19)
          - Mi-Mu, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 20)
          - Mc, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 21)
          - N, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 22)
          - O, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 23)
          - P-Q, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 24)
          - R, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 25)
          - Sa-Sm, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 26)
          - Sn-Sz, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 27)
          - T, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 28)
          - U-V, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 29)
          - W, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 30)
          - X-Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 31)
        - 1969, 22 folders
          - A, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 1)
          - B, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 2)
          - C, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 3)
          - D, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 4)
          - E, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 5)
          - F, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 6)
          - G, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 7)
          - H, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 8)
          - I, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 9)
          - J, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 10)
          - K, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 11)
          - L, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 12)
          - M, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 13)
          - N, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 14)
          - O, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 15)
          - P-Q, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 16)
          - R, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 17)
          - Sa-Sm, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 18)
          - Sn-Sz, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 19)
          - T, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 20)
          - U-W, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 21)
          - X-Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 22)
        - 1970, 21 folders
          - A, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 1)
          - B, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 2)
          - C, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 3)
          - D, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 4)
          - E, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 5)
          - F, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 6)
          - G, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 7)
          - H, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 8)
          - I-J, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 9)
          - K, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 10)
          - L, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 11)
          - M, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 12)
          - N, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 13)
          - O, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 14)
          - P-Q, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 15)
          - R, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 16)
          - Sa-Sm, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 17)
          - Sn-Sz, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 18)
          - T, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 19)
          - U-W, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 20)
          - X-Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 21)
        - 1971, portions of 2 boxes
          - A, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 22)
          - B, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 23)
          - C, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 24)
          - D, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 25)
          - E, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 26)
          - F, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 27)
          - G, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 28)
          - H, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 355, Folder 29)
          - I, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 1)
          - J, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 2)
          - K, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 3)
          - L, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 4)
          - M, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 5)
          - N, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 6)
          - O, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 7)
          - P-Q, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 8)
          - R, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 9)
          - Sa-Sm, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 10)
          - Sn-Sz, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 11)
          - T, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 12)
          - U-W, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 13)
          - X-Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 14)
        - 1972, 17 folders
          - D, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 15)
          - E, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 16)
          - F, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 17)
          - G, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 18)
          - H, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 19)
          - I, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 20)
          - J, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 21)
          - K, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 22)
          - L, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 23)
          - M, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 24)
          - N, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 25)
          - O, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 26)
          - P-Q, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 27)
          - R, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 28)
          - S, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 29)
          - T, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 30)
          - U-W, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 31)
        - 1974, 2 folders
          - A, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 1)
          - B, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 2)
        - 1975, 19 folders
          - A, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 3)
          - B, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 4)
          - C, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 5)
          - D, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 6)
          - E, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 7)
          - F, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 8)
          - G, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 9)
          - H, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 10)
          - I, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 11)
          - J-K, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 12)
          - L, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 13)
          - M, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 14)
          - N-O, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 15)
          - P-Q, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 16)
          - R, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 17)
          - S, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 18)
          - T, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 19)
          - U-W, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 20)
          - X-Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 21)
        - 1976, 19 folders
          - A, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 1)
          - B, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 2)
          - C, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 3)
          - D, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 4)
          - E, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 5)
          - F, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 6)
          - G, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 7)
          - H, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 8)
          - I, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 9)
          - J-K, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 10)
          - L, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 11)
          - M, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 12)
          - N-O, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 13)
          - P-Q, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 14)
          - R, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 15)
          - S, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 16)
          - T, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 17)
          - U-W, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 18)
          - X-Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 19)
        - 1977, portions of 2 boxes
          - A, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 20)
          - B, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 21)
          - C, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 22)
          - D, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 23)
          - E, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 24)
          - F, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 25)
          - G, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 26)
          - H, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 27)
          - I, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 28)
          - J-K, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 29)
          - L, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 359, Folder 1)
          - M, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 359, Folder 2)
          - N, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 359, Folder 3)
          - O, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 359, Folder 4)
          - P-Q, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 359, Folder 5)
          - R, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 359, Folder 6)
          - S, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 359, Folder 7)
          - T, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 359, Folder 8)
          - U-W, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 359, Folder 9)
          - X-Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 359, Folder 10)
        - 1978, portions of 2 boxes
          - A, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 359, Folder 11)
          - B, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 359, Folder 12)
          - C, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 359, Folder 13)
          - D, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 359, Folder 14)
          - E, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 359, Folder 15)
          - F, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 359, Folder 16)
          - G, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 359, Folder 17)
          - H, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 359, Folder 18)
          - I-K, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 1)
          - L, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 2)
          - M, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 3)
          - N, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 4)
          - O, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 5)
          - P-Q, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 6)
          - R, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 7)
          - S, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 8)
          - T, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 9)
          - U-W, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 10)
          - X-Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 11)
        - 1979, portions of 2 boxes
          - A, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 12)
          - B, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 13)
          - C, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 14)
          - D, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 15)
          - E, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 16)
          - F, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 17)
          - G, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 18)
          - H, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 19)
          - I-J, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 20)
          - K, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 21)
          - L, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 22)
          - M, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 23)
          - N, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 1)
          - O, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 2)
          - P-Q, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 3)
          - R, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 4)
          - S, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 5)
          - T, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 6)
          - U-W, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 7)
          - X-Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 8)
        - 1980, 19 folders
          - A, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 9)
          - B, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 10)
          - C, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 11)
          - D, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 12)
          - E, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 13)
          - F, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 14)
          - G, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 15)
          - H, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 16)
          - I-J, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 17)
          - K, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 18)
          - L, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 19)
          - M, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 20)
          - N, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 21)
          - O-P, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 22)
          - Q-R, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 23)
          - S, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 24)
          - T, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 25)
          - U-W, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 26)
          - X-Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 27)
        - 1981, 21 folders
          - A, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 1)
          - B, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 2)
          - C, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 3)
          - D, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 4)
          - E, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 5)
          - F, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 6)
          - G, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 7)
          - H, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 8)
          - I, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 9)
          - J, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 10)
          - K, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 11)
          - L, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 12)
          - M, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 13)
          - N, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 14)
          - O, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 15)
          - P-Q, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 16)
          - R, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 17)
          - S, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 18)
          - T, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 19)
          - U-W, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 20)
          - X-Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 21)
        - 1982, portions of 2 boxes
          - A, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 22)
          - B, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 23)
          - C, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 362, Folder 24)
          - D, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 1)
          - E, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 2)
          - F, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 3)
          - G, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 4)
          - H, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 5)
          - I, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 6)
          - J, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 7)
          - K, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 8)
          - L, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 9)
          - M, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 10)
          - N, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 11)
          - O, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 12)
          - P-Q, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 13)
          - R, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 14)
          - S, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 15)
          - T, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 16)
          - U-W, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 17)
          - X-Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 18)
        - 1983, portions of 2 boxes
          - A, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 19)
          - B, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 20)
          - C, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 21)
          - D, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 22)
          - E, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 23)
          - F, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 24)
          - G, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 25)
          - H, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 26)
          - I, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 27)
          - J, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 364, Folder 1)
          - K, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 364, Folder 2)
          - L, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 364, Folder 3)
          - M, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 364, Folder 4)
          - N, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 364, Folder 5)
          - O, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 364, Folder 6)
          - P-Q, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 364, Folder 7)
          - R, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 364, Folder 8)
          - S, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 364, Folder 9)
          - T, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 364, Folder 10)
          - U, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 364, Folder 11)
          - V, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 364, Folder 12)
          - W-X, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 364, Folder 13)
          - Y-Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 364, Folder 14)
      - Camps, Miriam, 1973-1995; 2 folders (Box 364, Folder 15 to 16)
      - White, Eric Wyndham, 1966-1968; 1 folder (Box 364, Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous, 1935-2000; 4 boxes (1 partial)
        - 1935-1936, 1 folder (Box 364, Folder 18)
        - 1941, 1 folder (Box 364, Folder 19)
        - 1942, 1 folder (Box 364, Folder 20)
        - 1943, 1 folder (Box 364, Folder 21)
        - 1945, 1 folder (Box 364, Folder 22)
        - 1946, 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 1)
        - 1947, 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 2)
        - 1948, 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 3)
        - 1949, 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 4)
        - 1950, 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 5)
        - 1951, 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 6)
        - 1952, 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 7)
        - 1953, 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 8)
        - 1954, 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 9)
        - 1955, 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 10)
        - 1956, 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 11)
        - 1957, 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 12)
        - 1958, 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 13)
        - 1959, 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 14)
        - 1960, 1 folder (Box 366, Folder 1)
        - 1962, 1 folder (Box 366, Folder 2)
        - 1963, 1 folder (Box 366, Folder 3)
        - 1966, 1 folder (Box 366, Folder 4)
        - 1967, 1 folder (Box 366, Folder 5)
        - 1968, 1 folder (Box 366, Folder 6)